

Lora Milcheva

+359 887 718 788 lora.milcheva@outlook.com

ABOUT

Hello,

My name is Lora Milcheva and I am a graphic designer and frontend developer. I'm born in Sofia and I'm 39 years old. For the past two years I've been taking care of my little child and my family.

I recently completed my education in Digital Marketing and Search Engine Optimization, which gave me fundamental knowledge about modern marketing in the digital world and, also, helped me build a better approach in my work.

As a designer I am keen on creating. That's why I really enjoy writing code and experimenting with vision and functionality. I appreciate impressive, yet simple and clean design, combining good structure, consistency and usability.



SKILLS

Graphic Design

Adobe Photoshop	excellent
Adobe InDesign	excellent
Adobe Illustrator	very good

Web Development

JavaScript	very good
React	very good
Angular	basic
HTML + CSS	very good
Sass	basic
Bootstrap	very good



EDUCATION

March 2020 – August 2021 SofUni Digital

Digital Marketing. SEO.

January 2017 – April 2018 **Software University**

JavaScript Developer

October 2000 – July 2004 **New Bulgarian University**

Graphic Design - Bachelor

September 1996 – June 2000 II English Language School

High School

EXPERIENCE

October 2013 – August 2019 Freelance

Graphic & Web Design. Front-end Development.

April 2008 – September 2013 Exzayl Ltd.

Co-founder. Graphic Designer.

October 2004 – April 2008 **Cores Business Centres**

Graphic Designer